magicmadhouse.co.uk 2016-07-02

# Magic Madhouse Private Policy | Private Policy Magic Madhouse

Magic Madhouse is committed to ensuring your privacy is protected. We use information in accordance with the Data Protection Act 1998.

When placing an order or using an online form on our website we need to know your name and other information such as postal address, e-mail address, telephone number and credit card details etc. We gather this information to fulfil your request and communicate with you on the matter at hand.

We use certain third parties to carry out tasks on our behalf. Activities typically involved include, delivering consignments, fulfilling orders, sending e-mails, processing credit card payments, and maintaining our customer database. These third parties have access to this information purely on the basis of conducting tasks on Magic Madhouse’s instructions, not for their own use. We won't disclose your personal information unless obliged to, or allowed to do so by law, or where we need to in order to run our business (e.g. where other people process data for us). In such circumstances, we ask those people to give us confidentiality or non-disclosure undertakings.

We also collect information concerning your marketing preferences. We will from time to time contact you with targeted offers and information relating to product range updates but will do so in accordance with your preferences. You can opt-in and out at any time and can do so by contacting us online or for those who are logged in, editing your preferences in the ‘My Account’ section. (check what is available).

## How do we use your personal data?

Where appropriate, we use your personal data:

  * to provide goods and services to you or your organisation;
  * for basic profiling purposes;
  * to let you know about other goods and services in which you may be interested;
  * to inform you about changes and improvements to this website.

If you register or place an order, you will receive email communications alerting you to news and offers. You may choose not to receive these.

## Links

This site contains links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of these and you should read their own privacy policies. The policy described here, applies only to personal data collected by Magic Madhouse.

## Inaccuracies and corrections

We aim to keep your personal data accurate and up to date. If you become aware of errors or inaccuracies, please contact us.

## Changes to this policy

The Magic Madhouse privacy policy may change at any time, so you may wish to check it each time you visit our website.

## Cookies

There is some mystery surrounding what a cookie actually is but it in simple terms it is a piece of data stored on your computer that acts as an identifier for when you visit the site again. A link is made between you and the information you have provided to the website through the cookie. Certain advantages of cookies are that it helps keep your shopping basket separate from other users, keeps items in your basket between visits and offers an express checkout option.

It should be noted that cookies do not contain any personally identifying or financial information. The majority of web browsers automatically accept cookies; however your web browser can be altered to not accept them. If cookies are blocked it does prevent certain features of the website from working correctly
